  export interface Qstn {
    question: string;
    options: string[];
    correctOption: number;
    points: number;
  }
  export  const qstns: Qstn[] =[
      {
        "question": "What does kemish love mostly for his lunch?",
        "options": ["cauli", "roast", "simple rice", "fried potato"],
        "correctOption": 3,
        "points": 10
      },
      {
        "question": "Which is the longest river in Earth?",
        "options": ["Nile", "Amazon", "Koshi", "Singzilla"],
        "correctOption": 0,
        "points": 10
      },
      {
        "question": "How many districts are there in Nepal?",
        "options": ["74", "75", "76", "77"],
        "correctOption": 3,
        "points": 10
      },
      {
        "question": "To visit Mustang  from ktm,how many districts you have to cross?",
        "options": ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
        "correctOption": 3,
        "points": 10
      },
      {
        "question": "Which country is Nepal bordered in the South East?",
        "options": ["India", "Bangaladesh", "China", "USA"],
        "correctOption": 0,
        "points": 10
      },
      {
        "question": "Which place has the highest number of temples?",
        "options": [
          "ktm",
          "Delhi",
          "Damascus",
          "Varanasi"
        ],
        "correctOption": 0,
        "points": 10
      },
      {
        "question": "When was PN shah born?",
        "options": ["1779", "1780", "1781", "1778"],
        "correctOption": 0,
        "points": 10
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the next number in the series: 2, 6, 12, 20, ___?",
        "options": [
          "24",
          "30",
          "36",
          "42"
        ],
        "correctOption": 1,
        "points": 30
      },
      {
        "question": "If a plane crashes on the border of the United States and Canada, where do they bury the survivors?",
        "options": [
          " United States",
          "Canada",
          "Nowhere, survivors are not buried",
          "In a cemetery"
        ],
        "correctOption": 2,
        "points": 20
      },
      {
        "question": "when i was 4 my sis was 2.Now i am 6, my sis is?",
        "options": [
          "2",
          "3",
          "4",
          "5"
        ],
        "correctOption": 2,
        "points": 20
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is the singer of moye moye song?",
        "options": [
          "Blackpink",
          "Dilher mehendi",
          "Atif aslam",
          "Dzanum"
        ],
        "correctOption": 3,
        "points": 30
      },
      {
        "question": "If you rearrange the letters 'CIFAIPC', you would get the name of a:?",
        "options": [
          "Country",
          "City",
          "Animal",
          "Ocean"
        ],
        "correctOption": 3,
        "points": 30
      },
    
      {
        "question": "I am an odd prime number. If you double me and add 1, you get a square number. What number am I?",
        "options": [
          "Footsteps",
          "Memories",
          "Time",
          "Breath"
        ],
        "correctOption": 0,
        "points": 30
      },
      {
        "question": "Kemish is?",
        "options": [
          "A person",
          "Word",
          "Name",
          "I dont know."
        ],
        "correctOption": 1,
        "points": 30
      },
      {
        "question": "if a sun goes blackout and again shines how much time we would be without sunlight?",
        "options": [
          "8 seconds",
          "8 minutes",
          "8 days",
          "8 weeks"
        ],
        "correctOption": 1,
        "points": 20
      }
    ]
  
  export default qstns;